[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What South American island is shared by Chile and Argentina?", "correct_answer": "Tierra Del Fuego", "incorrect_answers": ["Islas Malvinas", "Islas Galapagos", "Isla De Pascua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the fancy Carmen: A Hip Hopera club where Carmen meets Blaze for the first time?", "correct_answer": "The Spot", "incorrect_answers": ["Blazer", "Lous", "Cherrys"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor co-wrote the 1985 movie Rambo: First Blood Part II together with James Cameron?", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone", "incorrect_answers": ["Arnold Schwarzenegger", "Mel Gibson", "Bruce Willis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This great inventor loved the number three and would only stay in hotel rooms with a number divisible by three.", "correct_answer": "N. Tesla", "incorrect_answers": ["T .A. Edison", "E. Howe", "M. E. Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The praying mantis lives only up to one year.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This award-winning composer/arranger has written and arranged the themes for St. Elsewhere, Law and Order, NYPD Blue, Toma, The Rockford Files and several other great TV shows.", "correct_answer": "Mike Post", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Vita", "Danny Lux", "Danny Elfman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lower frequencies have longer wavelengths, while higher frequencies have shorter wavelengths.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Ben when he returns to MIT in the movie 21?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["He finds out his winnings are gone from his room.", "He offers Rosa to join the team for a final hit in Vegas.", "He finds a note telling him he cant graduate."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What internal organs are some gold salts, such as potassium gold cyanide, toxic for?", "correct_answer": "Kidneys and liver", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Brain and skin", "Lungs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many points are required to open with 1 No Trump opening bid according to the standards of the bridge bidding system Acol?", "correct_answer": "15-17 points", "incorrect_answers": ["12-14 points", "13-19 points", "13-14 points"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The geographic North and South Poles are at fixed locations and have not moved.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many English words (not proper nouns) begin with dw?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "6", "5"]}]